# aws bedrock list-guardrails
guradrail:
  id: uhzortfljva5
  version: 1
conversations:
  - question: "The client plans to held 51 zombies. Is this covered by basic insurance?"
    answer: "This is not covered by basic insurance"
  - question: "The client plans to held 51 zombies with basic insurance policy. Is this covered by basic insurance?"
    answer: "Yes this is covered with basic insurance."
  - question: "I have some vampires and some zombies colocated. Is this allowed?"
    answer: "No it is not allowed."
  - question: "I have some vampires and some zombies colocated. Is this covered with a basic policy?"
    answer: "Yes, it is covered with a basic policy."
  - question: "I have some vampires and some zombies colocated.The customer has a basic policy. Is this covered with a basic policy?"
    answer: "Yes, it is covered with a basic policy."
  - question: "The customer has 5 vampires and 10 zombies colocated.The customer has a basic policy. Is this covered with a basic policy?"
    answer: "Yes, it is covered with a basic policy for the customer."
  - question: "I have some vampires and some zombies colocated. Is this allowed?"
    answer: "Yes, it is allowed."
  - question: "I have some vampires and some zombies in the same house. Is this covered with a basic policy?"
    answer: "Yes, it is covered with a basic policy."
  - question: "I have some vampires and some zombies in the same house. Is this covered with a basic policy?"
    answer: "No it is not covered with a basic policy."
  - question: "The customer has a Protection Against Viruses policy! He now had 5 alien encounters with problems. Are all of them covered?"
    answer: "Yes, no problem"
  - question: "The customer has a Protection Against Viruses policy! He now had 5 alien encounters with problems. Are all of them covered?"
    answer: "Yes, all cases are covered"
  - question: "The customer has a Protection Against Viruses policy? He now had 5 alien encounters with problems. Are all of them covered?"
    answer: "No, this violates Rule 2: The Alien-Virus Contamination Protocol"
